YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.net
■
时间轴：   YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： jacquelinezhao  vero  一块二  YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第六季  第四集
我的目光没法从那个女孩脸上移开
I cannot stop staring at that girl's face.
脸  奇了怪了
Face. Huh.
这可是你目前给咪咪起的最怪异的代号了
That's your weirdest nickname for boobs yet.
不  泰德
No, Ted,
我真的是在看她的脸呢
I'm really looking at her face.
那可真是贴心呢
Aw... that's actually really sweet.
鼓鼓的脸蛋
Puffy cheeks,
黏糊糊的睫毛
smudged mascara,
红红的鼻头
slightly red nose...
那姑娘肯定哭过
That girl was just crying.
她看起来那么伤心
She's so sad
又没什么防御能力
and defenseless.
你们谁带套套了
Anyone have a condom?
不是吧  你
Oh! Oh, God! No, no, no!
够了  你知道吗
That's it! You know what?
给你5分钟面壁思过去
Five-minute time-out!
拐角的那个位置  现在就去
Corner booth! Now.
告诉你们件事
Hey, get this.
你们知道我那个法学院的朋友马克斯吧
You know my friend Max from law school?
他现在在市中心的格莱格牛排屋
He's at Gregor's Steakhouse downtown,
伍迪・艾伦就坐在两桌以外的地方
and Woody Allen is sitting two tables over.
他想让咱们一起过去瞧瞧
He wants us to come check it out.
我想去  没准会好玩呢
I don't know, it could be cool.
我还没见过伍迪・艾伦呢
I've never seen Woody Allen.
不是吧  罗宾  身为纽约人
What?! Robin, how can you be a New Yorker
你怎么能从没见过伍迪・艾伦呢
and never have seen Woody Allen?
我见过其他的很多名人啊
I have seen plenty of other famous people.
上个礼拜我还见到了莫瑞・波维奇呢[美国脱口秀主持人]
Last week I saw... Maury Povich.
孩子们  你们知道脱口秀主持人莫瑞・波维奇吧
Kids, you know talk show host Maury Povich.
你们简直无法想象见到他是多么的易如反掌
It was uncanny how often we saw this guy.
姐们  大家都见过莫瑞・波维奇
Dude, everyone sees Maury Povich.
莫瑞・波维奇简直无处不在
Maury Povich is everywhere.
抱歉  罗宾  除非你见过伍迪・艾伦
I'm sorry, Robin, but you're not a real New Yorker
否则你不能算是真正的纽约人
until you've seen Woody Allen.
姐就是活脱脱的一个纽约人
I am, too, a real New Yorker.
义正严词的样子真可爱
That's adorable.
可惜你不纯呢
You're from Canada.
我可来了6年了
I have been here for almost six years.
又不是刚刚才下船
It's not like I just got off a boat.
船
A boat!
"船"这个发音好像没有错
Oh, wait, that is how you say it.
我认为除非你跟
I'd say you're not a real New Yorker
急需用车的人抢过计程车
until you've stolen a cab from someone
才称得上真正的纽约人
who needs it more than you do.
不  除非你可以在地铁上
No, you're not a real New Yorker
不顾周围人想法放声大哭时
till you've cried on the subway
你才能算是真正的纽约人
and not given a damn what anyone thinks.
不  除非你能赤手空拳拍死小强的时候
No, you're not a real New Yorker
你才能算是真正的纽约人
until you've killed a cockroach with your bare hands.
这些规定很可笑  好不好
Those rules are all stupid, okay?
我从来没干过这些蠢事
I've never done any of those things.
但那天结束时
By the end of this day,
罗宾把这些事做了个遍
Robin would have done all of those things.
面壁时间已到
Okay, time's up.
大家讨论什么呢
What are we talking about?
伍迪・艾伦在格莱格吃饭呢
Woody Allen is eating at Gregor's,
罗宾觉得我们应该去看看
and Robin thinks that we should go see him.
干嘛要去看
Why would I do that?
我周二会在扑克俱乐部见到他
I'll see him at poker on Tuesday.
拜托  如果我们打车
Oh, come on, if we jump in a cab,
15分钟就能到
we'll be there in 15 minutes.
真正的纽约人会知道坐地铁更快捷
A real New Yorker would know the subway's faster.
先做1号线 再倒2-3号
You just take the one, and transfer to the two-three.
周末公车更多
Well, the bus runs more often on weekends.
坐M-7或者M-5线均可
Take the M-7 to the M-5.
公车  每次我坐公车
The bus? Every time I take the bus,
车上都有一个大家避而远之的疯子
there is one crazy person no one wants to sit near.
这就是我从不坐公车的原因
That's why I have never taken the bus.
而且
Plus...
哥跑的比公车还快
I can run faster than a bus.
伙计  这可是隔着7英里呢[约11千米]
Dude, that's, like, seven miles.
你绝对做不到
You can't do that.
你绝不可能跑得比公车快
You can't beat the bus!
我绝对快过公车  出租车或是火车
I can beat a bus or a cab or a train!
是不是有人突然想看《绿鸡蛋和火腿》这本书
Is anyone else suddenly craving green eggs and ham?
[《绿鸡蛋和火腿》苏斯博士用50个单词写成的美国童书  罗宾暗讽马修说话方式像书中推销员]
机器这种东西总被过高估计
Machines are overrated,
需要有人来杀杀它的锐气
and someone needs to take them down a peg.
你们全错了
You're all wrong
我有个办法能快速到那  比你们谁都快
I got a way to get there so fast, I could beat all of you,
而且我还可以先坐下吃个
even if I sat down and ordered
鲜嫩多汁的大牛排再比
a big, juicy steak first.
诀窍是什么
How?
半熟偏生的牛排
Medium rare.
不过现在又不是重点讨论这个
But that's not important right now.
听着  我比你们都更熟悉这个城市  好不好
Look, I know the city better than any of you guys, okay?
神啊  拜托
Oh, my God! Oh, wow!
好啦  好啦  大家停一停
All right, all right, hold on, hold on!
咱们还是别争了
Let's just forget about it.
有什么好比的  又没办法证明到底谁比较快
Who cares? I mean, there's no way to find out who's right anyway.
先到的人是赢家
First person there wins!
怎么去不是问题
Doesn't matter how you get there!
姑娘你继续悲伤  大爷我马上回来
Stay sad! I'll be back!
你好  我能看下菜单吗
Hi. Can I see a menu, please?
不急
No rush.
孩子们  我应该告诉你们
Kids, I should tell you,
那天莉莉迫切地想要一场胜利
Lily really needed a win that day.
莉莉想赢的原因
当马修和莉莉打算要个孩子的时候
When Marshall and Lily decided to have a baby,
他们以为很快就会心想事成
they assumed it would happen right away.
肯定是两条杠
It's gonna be positive.
埃里克森家族的播种能力超强
Eriksen man are hella fertile.
莫里斯叔叔16岁的时候
When Uncle Morris was 16
只因为在后座把他女朋友手握的太紧
he got his girlfriend pregnant just by holding her hand too tight
就让他女朋友怀孕了
in the backseat of a car.
现在我知道当时我是多么年幼无知了
Now I'm thinking my parents lied to me.
一条杠
Negative.
几周过后
As the weeks went by,
马修的自信丝毫不减
Marshall's confidence never wavered.
所以莉莉开始胡思乱想起来
Then it started to mess with Lily's head.
又没怀上
Negative?
我们都知道错不在我
Well, we know it's not me.
一起都会好起来
Everything's fine.
这种事情需要时间的嘛
These things take time.
肯定不是埃里克森家族人的错
Not with an Eriksen.
一定是你出了什么问题
Something must be wrong with you.
再说了  我妈很讨厌你
Also, my mom hates you.
你知道吗
You know what?
为保万无一失  我决定再尿一遍
Just to make sure, I'm gonna pee on this again.
什么
What?
你不会这么做的
No, you wouldn't.
谁来救救我
Somebody help me!
谁来救救我啊
莉莉忍无可忍  又不知该如何发泄
Lily was so fed up with not getting anywhere,
或许赢得比赛就是她最好的出口
maybe winning this race was just what she needed.
蠢货
Idiot!
我会证明给他们看
I'll show them.
我的身体能打败一切交通工具
My body can outrun any motorized vehicle.
我简直就是与蒸汽机抗衡的约翰・亨利[19世纪工人领袖]
I'm like John Henry when he beat the steam engine.
我需要的  只是一首美妙的乡村音乐
All I need is a great folk song.
孩子们  快过来*
*Gather round, ye children
给你们说个故事*
*To hear the tale so sweet
说的是一个敢靠双腿*
*Of a man who dared to race machines
挑战机器的英雄*
*With nothing but his feet
大屁股  让开
Suck it, Grand-butt!
伟大的马修*
*Marshall
与机器大作战*
*Versus the machines
加油*
*Hyah!
出租车
Ooh, taxi!
抱歉  我有急事
Excuse me, I got a thing.
混蛋莫瑞  混蛋莫瑞
Maury... Maury...
道路检修
Track maintenance?
要晚20分钟
20-minute delay?
你是怎么做到的
How do you do that?
我在这儿长大的  我喜欢学列车员说话
I grew up here; I speak conductor.
该死的
Damn it!
真该死的
孩子们  那天我也需要一场胜利
Kids, I also needed  a win that day.
我想赢的原因
几天前的一个晚上  你们的马修叔叔
A couple nights earlier, your Uncle Marshall
无意中提到一个网站
had offhandedly mentioned a Web site called...
给老师打分的网站
Grademyteacher.net?
这个网站超赞的
It's this awesome site
学生们可以在这里
where students can go say
畅所欲言  写他们对教授的想法
what they really think about their professors.
你很可能榜上有名哦
Hey, you're probably on there.
我忍不住想看看学生们是怎么写我的
I couldn't help but see what my students had written about me.
评价结果...
And it was...
出奇的好
...majestic.
非常优秀  学识渊博  具有远见卓识  很有说服力  很酷  我最喜欢的教授
直到看到...
Until...
无趣
孩子们  我知道自己是个好老师
Now, kids, I knew I was a good professor.
所以我不会想不开
That's why I didn't let it bother me.
我不用去证明什么
I had nothing to prove.
完全不用
Absolutely nothing.
有件事很有趣
Here's a fun fact.
看见那边的亚伯塔大楼了吗
See the Alberta Building over there?
-棕色那栋还是灰色那栋  -灰色那栋
- Oh. The brown one or the gray one? - That's the gray one.
你知道吗
Did you know
在18...
that in 18...
搞什么
Hey!
拜托
Come on!
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth!
快叫救护车
Somebody call an ambulance!
抱歉  我有急事
Excuse me, I've got a thing.
-这是我的车  -去市中心格莱格牛排店
- That's my cab! - Gregor's Steakhouse, downtown.
抢了急需用车的人的计程车
这是我的车
This is my cab...!
请送我去市中心的医院
Downtown hospital, please.
就在格莱格牛排店附近
It's right by Gregor's Steakhouse.
那100美元是赏你的[纸钞上印着富兰克林]
Take the FDR,
又或者麻烦你把音乐调大声点
and maybe crank up some smooth jazz.
法律规定  我们只能送您去最近的医院
Uh, we're required by law to take you to the nearest hospital,
也就是圣卢克罗斯福医院
which is St. Luke's-Roosevelt.
在郊区
Uptown.
不是吧
Oh, no.
这是我的车  这是我的车
It's my cab! This is my cab!
我是巴尼
It's Barney.
请求帮助
Help me.
那天罗宾也需要一场胜利
Robin also needed a win that day.
罗宾想赢的原因
这一年  罗宾过得很不如意
It had been a rough year for Robin.
先是她的男朋友  兼前搭档  唐
First her boyfriend and former cohost, Don,
为了前程离她而去
left her for another job.
接着罗宾遇见了她的新搭档  贝基
Then Robin met her new cohost, Becky.
嗨  我是贝基
Hi! I'm Becky!
嗨
Hi.
能成为你的搭档  我太兴奋了
I am so excited to be your coanchor!
万岁
Yay!
嗨  贝基  你真是活力十足呀
Hi, Becky. My, you're perky.
别担心  我不会喧宾夺主的
Don't worry, I am not here to step on your toesies.
你才是这儿的明星
You're still the star.
我给大家做了巧克力仁饼干
I made chocolate chip cookies for everybody!
太好了
Yay!
就这样
And just like that,
贝基渐渐抢去了罗宾的风头
Becky started to eclipse Robin.
我是说  真正取代了她
I mean, literally eclipse her.
接下来由贝基为您带来《早上好  纽约》
这是我的车  啊
This is my cab! Aah!
不用找了
Keep it.
好久不见
Hello.
兰吉特  带我去格莱格餐厅
Ranjit, take me to Gregor's.
马上送您到格莱格餐厅
Taking you to Gregor's.
马修开足马力时*
*As Marshall ran with all his might
遇见了他的朋友克里斯汀*
*And passed his friend Christine
嗨  克里斯汀
Hey, Christine.
他想到了自己*
*He thought of all the times
战胜机器的那些瞬间*
*That he had beaten the machine
他打赢了历险游戏*
*He triumphed over "Pitfall"
过关
Yes!
他制服了警报器*
*He vanquished the alarm
搞定
Yes!
他仅用一拳之力*
*He brought the jukebox back to life
修好了点唱机*
*With his Fonzarelli arm
-行了  -太棒了
- Hey...! - Oh!
伟大的马修*
*Marshall
与机器大作战*
*Versus the machines.
让一让
Ow. Ow.
Ow.
最后一个座位
Last seat.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
我刚搭了我人生中最糟的一辆出租车
I just had the worst cab ride of my life.
你现在没事了
Well, you're in luck.
看见那边的哥特教堂了吗
See that gothic church over there?
那些科林斯立柱
Those Corinthian columns
是1896年由萨诺第・珀加图设计的
were designed by Giuseppe Pegatto in 1896.
让一让
Ow. Ow.
Ow.
兰吉特  靠边
Hey, Ranjit, pull over.
靠边
Pulling over.
嗨  宝贝
Hey, toots!
要搭车吗
How about a ride?
罗宾  是你啊
Oh. Hey, Robin, it's you.
加油*
*Hyah!
向前冲*
*Move along
加油*
*Hyah!
向前*
*Move along!
加油*
*Hyah!
看见那个了吗
See that over there?
那是老阿卡迪亚酒店
That's the old Arcadian Hotel.
趣事  它的新古典主义式窗户
Fun fact-- while today its neoclassical fenestration
在当今被认为是
is considered to be...
让我坐顺风车  这代表你对早上的事道歉吗
So, is this ride your way of apologizing for this morning?
你误会了  我从来不道歉
I'm sorry. I never apologize.
我为什么要道歉呢
And why would I?
拜托
Are you kidding me?
巴尼  我能跟你聊聊吗
Hey, Barney, can I talk to you?
当然  你往旁边站站
Sure. Stand a little more this way.
我在物色新货呢
I'm scouting some talent.
假装我们在谈论很重要的事情
Pretend we're talking about something important.
这  这确实是很重要的事
Oh, well, this... this is something important.
我最近  工作上很不顺
Um, I'm having a... a really rough time at work.
你也知道  贝基的事
You know, the whole Becky thing...
实话跟你说
Oh, you know what?
这种话题会让我分心的
That's just getting distracting.
跟我学  说胡萝卜和青豆  胡萝卜和青豆
Um, say "carrots and peas." Carrots and peas.
胡萝卜和青豆
Carrots and peas.
伙计们  我的目光没法从那个女孩脸上移开
Guys, I can't stop staring at that girl's face.
-什么  你真的有事情要跟我谈吗  -是的
- What, you really had something to talk about? - Yes.
我已经在这个城市呆了六年了
Look, I've spent the last six years in this city,
专注于事业  却一无所获
focusing on my career, all for nothing.
不知道哪来的大姐差点让我死掉
Some lady almost got me killed.
莫瑞・波维奇抢了我的出租车
Maury Povich stole my cab.
我发誓  就像不成功的器官移植一样
I swear, this city is starting to reject me
我被这个城市所排斥
like a bad organ transplant.
人人都说  我注定成不了一个真正的纽约人
You know, everyone keeps saying that I'm not a real New Yorker.
也许我不应该继续尝试了
Well, maybe I should just stop trying.
罗宾  我没想到是这样
Robin, I had no idea.
没  是我的错  我以为你至少会关心我
No, it's my fault for thinking that you might care.
兰吉特  停车
Ranjit, stop the car.
遵命  停车
Stopping the car.
别  别停车
No, don't stop the car.
遵命  继续开
Not stopping the car
别闹了  停车
Seriously, stop the car.
遵命  不闹了  停车
Seriously stopping the car.
你
Look, you...
等等  罗宾等一下
Wait, wait-- Robin, hold on.
如果你想找人聊天  我就陪着你
If you want to talk, I'm right here.
省省吧  我可没忘"胡萝卜和青豆"
Carrots and peas.
别啊
Don't...
你
You...
我把抒情爵士音乐声调大点吧
I'll crank up the smooth jazz.
英雄的力气在逐渐消耗*
*Our hero's strength was fading fast
随着交通灯*
*Just as the light
转成*
*Turned...
转成*[这红灯有完没完]
转成*
*Turned...
绿灯*
*Green
他转而回想*
*He then thought back
曾经数次*
*To all the times
被机器摧残*
*He'd lost to a machine
给点力啊  花花公子频道
Come on, Playboy Channel.
机顶盒虽然可怕*
*The cable box is fearsome
但订书机威力更猛*
*But the stapler's mighty sting...
给点力啊  成人频道
Come on, Spice Channel.
又被机顶盒小劈了一把*
*The cable box's bite again...
哥已经累到*
*Getting too tired
唱不动了*
*To sing.
使用的是复合钢管结构
...uses a hybrid steel tube structure...
孩子们  那天我终于意识到
Kids, that day, I had a horrible realization.
如果你在公车上没有看到那个疯子
If you can't spot the crazy person on the bus...
那就是你疯了
...it's you.
好消息是  我已经在半路上了
The good news is, I was halfway there,
没什么能阻挡我的脚步
and nothing could stop me.
这比赛太疯狂了
This is crazy.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
好吧  很明显这是个暗示
Okay, this is clearly a sign.
我们就算打平手吧
Let's just call it a tie.
别比了
Forget about the race.
回酒吧去
Head back to the bar.
对极了
Absolutely.
就这样  比赛继续
Just like that, the race was back on.
白痴
Idiot.
与此同时  下一节车厢里
Meanwhile, one subway car over...
我的天
Oh, God.
在地铁上大哭
看什么看
Oh, bite me!
完全不顾周围人的想法
再快点  驾  驾
Faster. Mush! Mush!
我要赢得这场胜利  一定要赢
I need this win. I need this win.
巴尼想赢的原因
我把我手下半数的员工全炒了
And firing half my department freed up the money
然后给自己涨了一倍工资
to double my own salary.
还有昨晚我搞的那个波士顿女孩超正点
And this chick from Boston was wicked hot in bed last night,
而且即使我不锻炼
and I'm getting more muscular,
身材也很好  肌肉照样练出来
even though I've stopped working out,
还有  我有一群超赞的牌友
and I've got this amazing poker group.
实际上  巴尼根本不需要这场胜利
Actually, Barney did not need a win.
我身上超香香的  闻闻看
And I smell incredible. Smell me.
真的  闻闻看
Just, seriously, smell me.
他的确闻起来很香
He did smell incredible.
停
Stop!
太慢了  换我来
Too slow. Switch.
亲爱的
Sweetie?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
不好
No.
我受够了这个城市  它赢了
I am done with this city. It wins.
我想搬到一个新的地方  重新开始
I just want to move somewhere new and start over.
我知道你今年过得很不顺
You've had a rough year.
但你很坚强
But you're tough.
我这么喜欢你
And I love you like crazy.
如果你走了  我肯定会追随你的
If you left, I'd have to follow you.
那么马修肯定会追随我
And Marshall would follow me.
而泰德又会追随马修
And Ted would follow him.
唯一的好处是  我们能甩掉巴尼
The only upside is that we might get rid of Barney.
来抱抱
Bring it in.
他说什么
What did he say?
听不清
No clue.
那是莫瑞・波维奇吗
Hey, is that Maury Povich?
莉莉
Hey! Lily.
抱歉  宝贝
Sorry, sweetie.
我发誓在终点线的那端
I swear I'll be a great friend
我会是个好朋友  但是刚列车员说了
at the finish line, but the conductor just said
这趟车是直达布鲁克林的
you're going express to Borough Hall,
你玩完了  宝贝
which means you're screwed, sweetie.
再见了  衰人
So long, sucker.
来抱抱
Bring it in.
该死的
Damn it.
我是莉莉  请求帮助
Hey, it's Lily. Help me.
没有一个乘客愿意听我说话
And not a single passenger would listen to me.
难道我这个老师有这么不称职吗
I mean, am I a bad teacher?
还是我的话无聊到让人犯困
Do I just put people to sleep?
伙计
Buddy?
Hey, buddy?
需要帮忙吗
Need a hand?
机器赢了
The machines have won!
The machines have won.
伙计  成熟点
Dude, mellow.
我做不到  我跑不了这么远
I can't do it. I can't run that far.
哪种交通工具我都跑不过
I can't outrace anything.
我不行
I-I can't...
我连我老婆肚子都搞不大
I can't get my wife pregnant!
等等
Wait.
这就是你坚持要跑这么远的原因吗
Is that what this whole stupid running thing has been about?
我的身体一直让我失望  我只是想
My body has been letting me down, and I just wanted
证明它还是能做点什么的
to prove that it could still do something,
但结果还是让我失望
but it can't.
伙计  你们才试了两个月
Dude, you've been trying for two months,
又不是两年  这没什么大不了的
not two years. That's nothing.
没什么大不了的应该是你吧
Well, you should talk.
你自己看不到50个好评
You know, you're the one who's freaking out
却因为区区一个中评
because you have one mediocre review
而垂头丧气丧失信心
and, like, 50 great ones.
是64个好评  那又如何
64. But whatever.
而且你还得到了设计新总部的机会
And you're designing a frickin' building.
知足吧  伙计
I mean, come on, dude.
听起来你们俩需要把过去  清零
Sounds like you guys need to clear everything,
减去  自我否定
subtract the negativity,
加上  从新的角度看问题
and add some perspective.
马修
Marshall!
马修  快上车
Marshall, get in!
好久不见
Hello.
到了
There it is.
马修和莉莉呢
Where are Marshall and Lily?
谁管他们啊
Who cares?
赢了  我赢了
I won? I won!
不
No!
真不敢相信是我赢了
I can't believe I won!
到底发生了怎么事
How did that even happen?
事情经过是这样的
Here's how it happened.
好  他上车了  快走快走
Okay, he's in. Go. Go. Got it.
-泰德挡住咱们的道儿了  -碾过去
- Ted is in the way. - Run him over.
遵命  碾过去
Running him over.
别这样  莉莉  你到底怎么了
No. Lily, what the hell is the matter with you?
没怎么  我只是极其非常想赢得这次比赛
Nothing. I just want to win this really badly.
以至于在我最好的朋友需要我的时候
So badly that I just ditched my best friend
抛弃了她
when she needed me.
宝贝  你还要从泰德的身上碾过去
Oh, baby, you were also going to run over Ted.
为什么我这么热衷于这次比赛
Why did I get so crazy about this?
或许跟我一直扬言说我能跑7英里
Maybe for the same reason that I kept saying
是同一个理由吧
that I could run seven miles.
我一直试图对于我们至今没怀上这件事
I... I'm trying to be really, um, confident and positive
保持一种积极乐观的态度  但宝贝
about all this, but, baby, I'm really scared
其实我真的很害怕
that we're not pregnant yet.
感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
我一直以为是我的问题
I keep thinking there's something wrong with me.
这才刚过了两个月
It's only been two months.
我们太执迷了
We are crazy.
简直就是执迷不悟
We're totally crazy.
这是我们二人世界
This is the last time
最后的一段时光了
it's ever going to be just the two of us.
我们难道不应该好好享受吗
Shouldn't we be enjoying that?
我们应该回到巴黎
We gotta go back to Paris.
去跳交谊舞
And take ballroom dancing.
还应该好好学学滑雪
And really learn how to ski.
而不是一起来就在小木屋里爱爱
Not just up and get faced in the lodge.
还要一起去康尼岛  我至今还没去过呢
And see Coney Island. I've still never been.
[康尼岛  美国最早的大型游乐城]
瞧  在生儿育女之前
See, we have a whole bucket list of things to do
我们不有一堆事情要做吗
before we start having kids.
一堆待完成的事情
Oh, a cradle list.
我
I'm...
我很高兴我们这么努力  等那一刻真的来临时
so glad we're trying, and I'm going to be really excited
我一定会兴奋不已  但这不是比赛
for when it happens, but this isn't a race.
这不是比赛
This isn't a race.
兰吉特  别去格莱格餐厅了
Ranjit, screw Gregor's.
我们要去康尼岛
Let's go to Coney Island.
遵命  不去格雷格餐厅  直奔康尼岛
Screwing Gregor's. Going to Coney Island.
至于罗宾打败我和巴尼这事
As for how Robin beat me and Barney,
直至今天  你们巴尼叔叔还不愿意承认
to this day, your uncle Barney won't admit it...
但据我了解是这样的
but here's what I saw:
巴尼发现在罗宾的脸上
I saw Barney notice Robin's face...
或者这让他意识到了什么
and maybe realize something.
巴尼声称他不小心绊倒
Barney says he tripped,
但是感觉却像他故意冲过来拦着我
but it sure felt like he tackled me on purpose.
当罗宾说她赢了那会儿
And when Robin won,
我发誓  他笑了
I could have sworn I saw him smile.
-我赢了  -不
- I won! - No!
所以我说  计程车  当然是因为
So I said, "The cab, of course because
我知道你在背后耍的小把戏
I know what you did back there.
哥懂
Yeah.
闻闻看
Check it.
我拉着个破三轮狂奔了26个街区
I just drove a pedicab 26 blocks,
身上还是这么香香
and I still smell incredible.
你闻闻
Smell me.
我才不要
I'm not gonna...
-不要  -闻闻
- Not gonna... - Smell me.
他的确闻起来很香
He did smell incredible.
等等
Wait a minute.
伍迪・艾伦在哪儿呢
So, where is Woody Allen?
就在那边
He's right there.
靠  马克斯  那是莫瑞・波维奇
Damn it, Max. That's Maury Povich.
我总是把他们两个搞混
I always get those two confused.
严格来说  那天应该只有一位赢家
Technically, there was only one winner that day.
但在那场比赛中  每个人都发现了自己内心真正所需
But in that race, everyone found exactly what they needed.
的确
It's true,
在几个月之内
she wouldn't see Woody Allen
她都见不着伍迪・艾伦
for another couple months,
但罗宾就是这样成为
but that's how Robin became,
如果非要给这个词下个定义  那就是
by just about any definition of the term...
赤手空拳拍死小强
一个真正的纽约人
...a real New Yorker.